Jane Rapley 547 Fulton St. E | Grand Rapids, MI 49503 | rapley.jane@gmail.com | 810-887-9269

Supply Chain Management

Upon graduating with a Bachelor's in Supply Chain Management I earned an internship with the City of Grand Rapids that has quickly grown into a full-time position. Which has given me experience in inventory management and warehousing. I would like to continue that focus and expand into other industries.

Core Competencies:

- Customer Service/Relations
- Project Management
- 5S
- Lean Principles

- Vendor Relations
- Inventory Management & Analysis
- Warehousing

- Purchasing
- Inventory Management Software
- MS Excel

Professional Experience

Storekeeper II

City of Grand Rapids – Water Department

Sept. 2015 - Present Grand Rapids, MI

- Manages the department's submissions of issues, audits, receiving, and invoicing.
- Create purchase orders daily to ensure inventory stays within target levels.
- Optimized city's database to assist field-employees with work orders.
- Key player in city-wide audit, resulting in better visibility to city's total inventory.

Intern

City of Grand Rapids – Water & Traffic Department

Apr. 2015 - Sept. 2015

Grand Rapids, MI

- Helped with Kaizen projects in the Water and Traffic stockrooms.
- Assisted the Inventory and Asset Manager with improvements to the inventory management program.
- Completed city's Gemba training program covering kaizen and 5S principles.

Cast Member

Celebration Cinema Woodland

Feb. 2014 - Apr. 2015

Grand Rapids, MI

- Provide guests with celebrated service through extra miles, high energy, and knowledge of operations.
- Consistently kept the scullery stocked to prepare for concession shifts.
- Responsible for training and mentoring new cast members.

Skills and Leadership

Silver Lake Conference Center

Summer 2010 & 2011

- First United Church of Christ Volunteer Camp Counselor.
- Responsible for 8 children between the ages of 9 and 11.

Systems

- Proficient in both Windows and Mac operating systems including Excel, Word, and Power point.
- Advantage 360 and Cityworks (Inventory Management Programs).

Education

Bachelors of Business Administration, Supply Chain Management, Grand Valley State University